The next thing to do is just to slice up or chop up a white onion.
I like to use a white onion because the color contrast is better.
The flavor is not that much different from a yellow onion; to me it just looks better.
So that is why I use a white onion, I already chopped it up and add maybe about a half of onion to this.
The next thing that I add is a chopped tomato now I used this is a regular tomato just a salad tomato.
I actually got an Italian tomato.
Those are plumb tomatoes I use those this time.
The reason is because they were redder fresher and they smell better.
Whenever I get a tomato I always smell it to make sure that it has that tomato smell so we add all of this in.
Then the secret ingredient to this is going to be cilantro.
A cilantro is a interesting vegetable you got to really wash it well or you're going to find sand and grit in it, so wash it and stem it.